Let me tell you what we're facing out here with these men.
I think it's time you date an average guy.
Do you now?
My response?
I'm not an average woman.
And for the record, every man I have dated has been average and below.
I'm not exaggerating.
She ain't lying.
It's time I date the level of far above average excellence that I am.
Sensational.
Now that seems like a natural, succinct ending to a conversation that shouldn't have begun in the first place.
But no.
Yamanz comes back with, it sounds like it's time you date me.
We can start slow and converse through this app.
I don't give my number out to just anybody.
Anybody?
Maybe if you really put the work in, you will be able to get my contact info.
And I can pick your brain while we have brunch and or lunch.
Sir.
Yo.
I replied, it sounds like you don't get it.
To which he replied, it sounds like you don't understand that I take no as a challenge.
That sounds like, that sounds like, that sounds like a rapist.
Yeah.
I blame whatever broad got him thinking this highly of himself.
And you know who it is.
His mama.